There are two players in the game - Circle(O) and Plus(X).
They are competitors one for another.

Initially virtual pulpit is created:

 1 | 2 | 3
---|---|---
 4 | 5 | 6
---|---|---
 7 | 8 | 9

The program will ask you to choose a tile from among available ones - just type relevant number with your keyboard.
First turn is over.
Now your opposer begins. The flow is exactly the same unless all tiles are taken.

When the game ends? Just like in classic tic tac toe - once any of you reaches full line - either vertical or horizontal or oblique.